He's dead.
Mrs. He,
save me!
Don't be afraid,
Mrs. He.
I'll protect you.
Where are we?
The orphanage I lived in as a kid.
It's been abandoned for a long time.
Are you sure no one's here?
Even if there is,
it's a ghost.
How are you so good at this?
From now on,
we're in
the same boat.
You asked me to look out for
news about Liu Dan.
His family called me this morning
saying they haven't reached him
in a while
and are worried something happened.
The housekeeper's disappearance
must have something to do with Zhang Xin.
What exactly happened between them?
You're not trying to scare me
with candles again, are you?
Take them away.
Throw out all the candles in the house.
Throw them all away.
The housekeeper sends his regards.
Liu Dan!
Why are you bringing him up?
He gave me something very important.
He said...
What did he say?
If anything happens to me,
you must release this.
I guess
you know what this is.
Why would he team up with you?
If you really had something,
you would've released it already,
right?
Then let's wait and see.
No way.
Mrs. He,
do you know how cold it is underground?
He Shi,
I'm too tired.
Let's do it another day, He Shi.
What's wrong with you
so late at night?
I saw
the butler.
You must be dreaming.
Really.
He's haunting me now.
What should I do?
He's dead.
Why worry so much?
They actually killed the butler.
What are you doing?
Something unclean has appeared
in the house lately.
I specifically asked Dad
and got someone to perform a ritual.
I think the most unclean thing here
is you.
W-What
are you
looking at?
He's right behind you.
Don't move.
Let me listen.
He says
he was wronged.
W-What
nonsense are you talking about?
He's come for you.
You'll never shake him off
for the rest of your life.
Then what should I do?
Where did you bury him?
Tell me.
I buried him...
Take him out.
He
is...
What is
he doing?
He Shi,
this psychic seems
to really know everything.
Get out, all of you!
Yes.
What's going on?
Are you scared silly?
Doctor,
why has my dad been in the hospital
for so long this time?
When will he recover?
Miss,
there is actually something
the master hasn't told you.
With his current condition,
he urgently needs fresh bone marrow.
But bone marrow
isn't that easy to find.
And as his immediate family,
you should be the best match.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I'm willing to donate.
That's great.
Let's do a detailed physical examination.
This way, please.
What are you doing?
I know everything now.
To keep me away from He Yu,
you actually used such dirty tricks.
It was clearly Zhang Xin
who kicked you out.
Why are you coming to me?
You're still making excuses.
You don't even know
you're being played as a pawn.
With your dullness,
don't you know Zhang Xin
and He Shi are having an affair?
Zhang Xin kicked you out
because she wants He Shi all to herself.
Aren't they in that kind of relationship?
What about Master He?
In the He family,
do you think
there are any morals or ethics?
If you don't believe me,
you can go and verify it.
It won't be too late to kill me then.
Sir!
Sir,
Li Zhangxin's medical report is out.
According to the report,
her bone marrow is
a perfect match for yours.